Preliminary Inventory to the Pacific Gas and Electric Company Motion Picture Film 1960-1970
Hoover Institution Archives
- Motion picture films, 1962-1966
  - Politics 1966: Ronald Reagan, candidate for governor, California, November 3, 1966 (Reel 20)
    Part I sequence: Slates begin (00:36), camera pans audience, guests on stage (01:05), Sibley begins speaking, introduces guests (01:15), Sibley introduces Reagan (04:45), Reagan begins speaking (08:02), Sibley thanks Reagan on the conclusion of his speech (25:20), first question from audience (26:35).
    Part 2 sequence: Questions continue (00:12), Reagan concludes, gets a standing ovation, shakes hands of guests on stage, and exits stage (30:06), Sibley thanks Reagan and the audience (30:43), audience exits (31:45), closing credits (31:59).
  - Politics 1966: Election Post-Mortem, November 15, 1966 (Reel 21)
    One week after the November 1966 election in California, this panel of journalists discusses the issues and results of the statewide election, in which all but one of the incumbent constitutional officers were voted out of office. The role of television in the election is a frequent discussion item. The panelists are introduced as (1) Earl C. "Squire" Behrens, veteran political writer and political editor, San Francisco Chronicle; (2) De Van L. Shumway, Sacramento News Bureau manager and political correspondent for United Press-International; (3) Nancy Clark, member of the KPIX-TV "The Big News" reproting team and prominent television news commentator; (4) Jack McDowell, noted political observer and political editor, San Francisco Examiner; and (5) Richard C. Bergholz, syndicated columnist and political editor, Los Angeles Times. The panelists are introduced by the moderator, A. Ruric Todd. This is the final program in the "Politics '66" series, which was sponsored by PG and E in cooperation with the Pacific Service Employees Association, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers - Local 1245, and Engineers and Scientists of California. Duration: 00:54:28.
    Sequence: slates begin (00:38), scenes of audience and panelists take their seats on stage (01:44), Todd begins introductions of panelists (03:08), Todd asks first question about similarities to the election of 1958, when most incumbents were also swept out of office (11:45), the first panelist, Behrens, speaks (12:10), first question from the audience (27:34), Todd thanks the panelists and cosponsors (52:32), audience applauds and begins to exit (53:26), end credits (53:43).